[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
Being this soft,
can you really interrogate a suspect?
Are you serious, Inspector?
- Sh*t! - Sh*t! Get in there!
Mungkorn, are you okay?
Why did this have to happen again?
Did you do everything I told you?
Is it possible...
that you two haven't done everything exactly
- "Become one in the most intimate way." - "Become one in the most intimate way."
So, how do you do it?
(Have you ever watched porn?)
I'm ready to be yours, Inspector.
What are you talking about?
We need to become one
in the most intimate way to break the curse.
I'm ready.
Let's just get it over with.
Are you serious?
Aren't you afraid?
Of course I am.
But Lukplub said...
it would feel heartwarming.
Seriously, can I ask you something?
Have you never done it with anyone?
Come on,
no need to be shy. You can tell me.
Of course I'm shy.
I'm this old, but I've never even done it before.
That doesn't matter.
To do this,
you should do it with someone you actually have feelings for.
But if we don't do it, your bad luck won't go away.
You don't have to go along with my mom's crazy ideas.
She's getting old and starting to lose it.
I'm not going to take your virginity away
just because of some superstition my mom believes in.
Look, if you're going to sleep with me,
it should be because you really have feelings for me.
Or what?
Do you really want to do it?
Just save it for that special someone of yours.
Then what are you going to do?
Lady Pharada will definitely keep asking us about it.
Don't worry.
I have a plan.
- Hey, Cupid. - Yes?
Do you think Thear and Mungkorn
will agree to become one?
My Lady, with his luck plummeting like this,
if they still don't do it,
all we can do is pray.
I'm absolutely sure that...
Mom and Cupid are eavesdropping on us.
Mungkorn!
Are you ready to be mine yet?
I'm ready.
- My Lady! - What?
It sounds like something is happening.
Oh, Mungkorn.
Whoa, how can you be so fair-skinned?
You're so sexy.
I want to kiss you all over, Mungkorn.
Oh, wow.
You're so sexy and fair-skinned.
And you smell so good.
Oh my! Two police officers having....
I want to lick every inch of your body.
Look at those doe eyes and that tiny little figure.
Whoa, so sexy.
Did you really have to go that far?
Now compliment me.
Come on, compliment me.
Wow, your muscles are so big!
Oh, you've got an incredible body.
Every part of you is just so big.
Let's get even more intimate, Mungkorn.
Whoa, take it easy.
My lips can't take it anymore.
How are you such a great kisser?
- Mungkorn... - Oh, Inspector!
A mother's life, I tell you.
I used to only wait outside the disciplinary office.
Never thought I'd be waiting outside my own son's bedroom,
listening to him do things like this.
I think we've set the mood.
Let's get down to business.
Oh, Mungkorn!
Mungkorn...
This isn't a sports day rally!
What's with that clapping?
Just wing it!
Oh, Mungkorn! Ah!
Wait!
What kind of porn have you been watching?
But this is how they do it in porn.
What porn did you watch? Monkey porn?
It was human porn.
Why were you making those weird sounds?
Oh, Mungkorn! Ah!
Let me take a break. I'm exhausted.
What happened? Did they stop?
Maybe they're into roleplay? Like a mouth gag or something?
Oh...
Have you ever had a massage?
- And did it feel good? - Yeah.
Exactly. Turn your back to me.
- What are you doing? - Just turn around already.
Wow, Mungkorn. That's it!
Oh, that's the spot!
Do you like that?
It's amazing!
Oh, Mungkorn!
I don't think I can listen to this anymore.
Good heavens!
I'm done.
- My Lady... - What?
My Lady, keep listening.
Lie down.
Mungkorn!
Come here, Mungkorn.
I'm coming!
Just let it all out!
Come on, I'm almost there!
Don't hold back!
I'm coming, Mungkorn!
Yes! Yes!
I love you, Mungkorn.
I love you, too.
Good job.
That was more tiring than actually having sex.
I'd say...
they've become one in the most intimate way possible.
I hope your luck finally turns around.
Alright.
I'm happy now.
Let's go.
- My Lady! - Let's go.
(Yin as Theartha)
(War as Mungkorn)
(Shane as Phuwin)
(Boss as Lukplub)
(Kit as Kanin)
(Tang as Nadol)
(Tae as Saming)
Believe it or not, I'm still wiped out.
Age really makes a difference.
What's on your mind?
What kind of person do you like?
Me?
I like someone who's kind,
loves their family,
and doesn't give up easily.
Someone petite
and cute as well.
Most importantly,
they have to look Asian, too.
Why do you ask?
Well,
when we were faking it,
it looked like you had to use a lot of imagination.
If you had imagined doing it with me,
you wouldn't have been able to do it, right?
Having to put up with me for six months,
it must be quite uncomfortable for you.
So, if you want to talk to anyone during this time...
Hey.
I didn't think about it like that.
And I'm not uncomfortable, either.
Now that I think about it, I'm actually having fun.
I think we're good partners.
Partners?
Yeah.
We're partners,
and you're my teammate in fooling my mother.
Okay.
Don't overthink it.
We should just go to sleep.
Goodnight.
Careful, you might dream about me.
I really am the Cunning Inspector.
The weekend morning feels so refreshing!
Sh*t...
What the hell is this water?
Khaomao! Khaopuk!
Why did you leave the floor soaking wet like this?
Where are you guys?
Where are you?
If Mom slips, she'll end up bedridden.
The water is still running!
Sh*t!
Something's definitely not right.
Holy spirits, please help!
I already did everything you asked!
You're messing with me, aren't you?
It's safe this way.
F*ck!
No!
How did this even happen?
No, no, no!
Wait, no!
Mungkorn!
- Whoa, whoa! - Mungkorn!
What's wrong, Inspector?
Whoa!
Why is the kitchen such a total mess?
What were you trying to cook?
Hey, watch out.
What's wrong with you?
Death is literally hunting me down.
What are you talking about?
Mungkorn,
can you take time off work to look after me?
What reason should I give for my leave?
Boss assigned tasks outside of my duties
or taking leave to care for my dying husband?
What should I say?
How about saving the life of a cursed young man
who happens to be very handsome?
If I die, you'll become a widower.
Stop! Don't touch that thing.
Or what?
It almost sliced my junk off just now.
- How could a fan slice it? - No, stop!
- Slice it how? Like this? - Whoa, whoa!
That's too dangerous.
It's not even plugged in.
Are you cold?
Is this fork sharp?
It's just a regular fork.
Better not risk it.
Can you please feed me?
You're being way too dramatic.
I'm not. Didn't you see the kitchen?
I almost died in there.
Feed me, please.
You're actually good at taking care of your partner.
Be honest with me.
Have you ever dated someone?
Never.
I'm pretty shy.
I don't have the guts to make the first move.
Does that mean I'm your first?
Are you talking to anyone right now?
Well, I'm married to you. Who else would I be talking to?
This is just a fake marriage, remember?
I mean someone you actually like.
So you're saying that even though we're married,
we can still like and talk to other people?
Of course.
That's just how this Cunning Inspector is.
There's no one.
I don't have anyone I like yet.
Look, I've been thinking
that during these six months,
if either of us meets someone we really like
we should be able to talk to them.
Or if you ever feel uncomfortable around me,
you can just say so.
It's better if we're being honest with each other, right?
Actually, the reason I feel uncomfortable
is because I have to pretend to be in love with you.
It's exhausting.
What do you wanna do, then?
How about letting your guard down?
Anyone who spends time with me will fall for me eventually.
Right?
That bite just tasted way better all of a sudden.
Maybe because the fork can't hurt me now.
Give me another bite, please.
Look, my hands are still shaking.
Fine.
Mr. Thear, Miss Praewa is here to see you.
Sh*t, she came all the way to my house?
What should I do?
What am I going to do?
What do I do now?
In that case, I'll leave now.
You stay here and have fun with your girl.
Hey, Mungkorn! Wait.
What?
You need to help me.
Help with what?
Please...
pretend to be in love with me for a bit longer.
No way.
If she sees us and finds out,
she'll turn it into a huge deal.
- I'm leaving. - Please, I'm begging you.
So she'll finally leave me alone.
And then...
I can focus on you and only you.
What are you doing?
Thear!
What is going on here?
Oh, Praewa... What brings you here?
You said you'd text me after showering,
but it's been a whole week, and you still haven't replied.
Did it take you that long to shower?
Oh...
I was busy getting married.
What?
See? This is my love.
What are you doing?
Come on, honey.
We're both in the police force.
We understand each other so well, and we're a great match.
Most importantly, he's so protective and cares deeply about me.
I wouldn't go that far, honey.
But if anyone tries to mess with him,
I'm not going to let it slide.
Come here, honey.
- Yes? - You've got something on your lip.
Where?
Right...
here!
Wow, you taste so sweet.
I'm sorry, Praewa.
I don't think we can keep seeing each other anymore.
Please just move on.
Oh, wait a second.
Don't you dare tell anyone about this.
This is classified information.
You always have so many excuses.
My heart is literally breaking.
Why would I tell anyone? I'm too embarrassed.
- Praewa... Hold on! Come back! - Don't call my name!
- Praewa! - Stop calling me!
No!
Bye-bye.
Dodged another bullet.
Well done, honey.
Honey?
Why don't I feel that way at all?
I feel more like your servant,
your good-luck charm,
and your decoy date.
What do you mean?
What exactly am I to you?
Mungkorn...
Mungkorn, don't be afraid.
Just tell the truth about what's going on between you and Thear,
and everything will be fine.
If you don't stop messing with us,
I'll interrogate you, too.
"If you don't stop messing with us,
I'll interrogate you, too."
Oh, I'm shaking in my boots, you dork.
Thear and Mungkorn are innocent anyway.
- Mungkorn, tell the truth. - Please leave.
- Go! - What?
- I have to work. - Mungkorn!
How would you explain this?
- Sh*t. - Sh*t.
Mungkorn, are you okay?
I'm fine.
You bastard. You want me to get rough with you, huh?
Inspector!
Are you alright?
What exactly do you want me to explain?
Are you two spies for the Black Bull gang?
What?
Did you intentionally silence Ronnaphop?
Hold on, this is getting out of hand.
Did Thear make you do it,
or did you do it of your own free will?
Make me do what? What are you even talking about?
What is the secret between the two of you?
There really was nothing.
Giving a false statement is a crime.
Well...
I...
What about right now?
There is still nothing.
Dammit, this piece of junk!
Captain,
I think this thing is broken.
This machine only tells the truth.
What is the secret
between the two of you?
Whatever it is, just come clean.
Ugh!
I don't really know myself.
He just comes and goes as he pleases.
He's probably just playing with my feelings.
Wait...
Are you two in a relationship?
No, we're not.
We're just married.
Married?
It was a marriage to turn his luck around.
Now we're just waiting for the day we split up.
Don't worry.
I won't tell anyone.
Thank you, Captain.
I don't want to have any trouble with the inspector either.
But if you ever need to talk, you can talk to me.
Please feel free.
Thank you.
Oh, Mungkorn?
Why are you home so early today?
They sent me home while the case is under review.
What's with the sad face?
Come talk to me, dear.
What happened?
Lately, things seem strange between you and Thear.
Did you guys fail to become one?
It has nothing to do with that.
Nothing at all.
Then what is it, dear?
Or is it that Thear isn't taking good care of you?
If he's done anything wrong,
you can tell me. I'll deal with him for you.
Or are there women bothering you?
I'm just lonely.
Ever since I moved here,
I've felt like I don't quite belong.
But it's probably nothing. I think I'm just homesick.
See? He really isn't taking care of you well enough.
If you want to go home, then you should be allowed to go.
Thear, come here.
How did you know I was eavesdropping?
Mother knows best, you know?
You always do this when you've done something wrong.
What? I haven't done anything wrong.
Stop talking back.
Since you're free right now, take Mungkorn back home for a visit.
Mom, with my luck this bad, you want me to drive?
I'll end up in a fatal crash. No way.
Wait,
you've already become one.
How would you still have bad luck?
Become one?
Oh, right.
We have become one, haven't we?
I totally forgot. I was wrong.
Yes, we've done it.
Then that's settled.
Take him back home for a visit.
If there's any misunderstanding, talk it out.
If you've done anything wrong, apologize to him.
Do you understand what I'm saying?
Aren't you taking this a little too far?
It's like you love him more than me now.
I can't help it.
He's just so adorable.
(Phayao)
I told you not to wear the ring outside,
and you took it that seriously, huh?
It's a direct order from my boss.
I have to follow it.
I never thought of you as just a placeholder
or my decoy date.
The reason I'm always ordering you around
is simply because I enjoy teasing you.
You're actually pretty cute when you're annoyed.
But I know now that you don't like it.
I'm sorry for that.
When I told Praewa that you're my husband,
I just wanted to show you the respect you deserve.
I'll try my best to believe that.
If you don't believe me, look at this. Hang on.
Here.
I've texted every girl in my contacts
to tell them I'm already married.
See for yourself.
I'm not going to do that.
Just put it away.
Listen.
I just want you to know that if I'm ever serious about someone,
I'll be completely faithful and love them with all my heart.
I'll always respect the person I love.
Come on, Inspector.
You don't need to explain this to me.
It doesn't really matter to me anyway
because I'm not the one you love in the first place.
Well, just in case.
We never know what the future holds.
If you happen to fall in love with me,
at least you'll know
that I make a great lover.
And about that time you asked
if I had to use a lot of imagination,
do you want to know what was actually on my mind?
You were probably thinking of someone you actually like.
I was thinking about how nice it would be
if we could actually do it together
because we both wanted to, not just to fix my luck.
♪Trying...♪
♪Let me remind you what our deal was all about,♪
♪No falling in love, no feelings allowed♪
♪I'm just a name on your contract, you're just passing through,♪
♪So stay on your side, and I'll stay on mine, too♪
Mom!
I'm home.
- Missed you so much. - I missed you so much, sweetie.
Let me give you a kiss.
One more.
That's enough! Thear is watching.
One more right here.
Know your place, Inspector.
What's going on?
We just met at the wedding.
Why the rush to come back and see me?
Well, I missed you.
I was worried about you, too,
so he drove me here.
Hello, Mom.
Hello, dear.
Inspector,
- you shouldn't spoil him so much. - Hey!
It's alright, Mom.
I've wanted to visit his home for a while now.
Oh, you've come at the perfect time.
The temple here is holding a fair.
Why don't you take him there?
Mom, it's a temple fair, not a pub or a bar.
He wouldn't know how to have fun at a place like that.
Come on, I'm a simple guy.
I'm not that fancy.
I know how to enjoy a fair.
Let's take your things upstairs
and check out your bedroom.
I'm going to cook some delicious food for you.
Make me lots of food, Mom!
I've missed your cooking so much.
Alright, sweetie.
You'd better eat a lot, okay?
Alright, I'll go grab the bags.
Hey there, Hunglay!
How have you been, buddy?
Khao Jao!
My boy!
It's been so long.
I miss you so much!
Daddy misses you.
Look how much you've grown.
I missed you so much.
Is this your cat? He's cute.
Yes.
He was a stray.
But after a while, he basically became my son.
What was his name again? Khao Jao?
- Can you salute for me? - Hello, sir!
Hello. Salute!
Oh, Inspector.
Please pass me that VIF Jelly.
That red pouch right there.
- This one? - Yes.
Want me to tear it open?
Yes, please.
Come here.
Thank you.
Now I know...
why you always have cat food with you.
You're just like a cat.
That's why you attract them.
Wanna try this? Meow!
Wanna try? I'll open it for you.
Just feed Khao Jao.
Khao Jao...
Have you been getting any treats?
The house is a bit old.
Come to think about it,
my whole house is smaller than your kitchen.
Why are you comparing them?
I think it's quite cozy.
It is cozy,
but I've always wanted a big house
to give my mom a safe, comfortable home.
Well, you'll be getting your marriage money soon.
You can get her a new house. I'll be the one footing the bill.
Come on, let me help you unpack.
Let me put this here.
(Pol.Snr.Sgt.Maj. Worawit Phianwanich, Deceased January 27, 2005)
Is this your dad, Mungkorn?
Yes.
My dad was a police officer, too.
(Pol.Snr.Sgt.Maj. Worawit Phianwanich, Deceased January 27, 2005)
How did he pass away?
He was shot.
He was an incredibly honest officer,
and that made him a target for a lot of people.
(Pol.Snr.Sgt.Maj. Worawit Phianwanich, Deceased January 27, 2005)
It's because of him...
that I want to be a good cop.
I want to follow in his footsteps and make him proud,
but my mom tried to stop me.
She's afraid I'll end up just like him.
You're a good cop, though.
I'm sure your dad would be so proud of you.
Wait, you play the guitar, too?
Yeah.
If I weren't a cop,
I'd probably be a musician by now.
Play something for me, then.
The thing is, I'm not in the mood.
I only play when the mood strikes.
Oh, really?
You have to wait for the mood, huh?
Alright, then.
Then I'll get you in the mood myself.
What should I do?
Does this get you in the mood?
What are you doing?
Can you sleep like this...
on a floor mattress under a mosquito net?
I'll let you sleep by yourself tonight.
I'll sleep in my mom's room.
No way.
You have to sleep with me.
I'm too scared to sleep alone.
I'm not used to this place.
And...
I need some warmth from you.
Nothing moved.
Back before the police exam,
I used to practice with an airsoft gun,
using these tin cans as targets.
But no matter how much I practiced, I could never hit them.
I'm not as good as you.
Well, nobody needs to be good at everything,
but I think everyone has at least one thing they're good at.
What would you say you're good at, then?
I think I'm good at...
I'm good at making people fall for me.
Anyone who gets close to me ends up falling for me.
I never miss a target I set my sight on.
Who exactly told you that?
Got some kind of certification to prove it?
I don't need anyone to tell me.
I can see it for myself, and I can feel it.
I think the only thing you're truly an expert at
is imagining things.
You don't have to wrap your arms around me.
I don't think I'm just imagining things.
Time to eat, guys.
Dinner's ready.
Coming, Mom.
- Let's go. - Let's go.
Hey.
Here, try some nam prik num.
Thank you.
You have to try this one, though,
because it's Mungkorn's favorite.
It's called ab ong-or.
What was it again? Ab...
- Ab ong-or. - Ab ong-or...
- Right. - Whoa, that's new.
Let me see.
This is delicious.
I haven't had Northern food
this authentic in a long time.
What?
You're from the North, but you barely eat Northern food?
That's just how I am.
I never realize how good the things right in front of me are
until I try them and get hooked.
Mungkorn knows how to cook Northern food, too.
You should cook for him sometime.
You've got some cooking skills of your own.
That's true.
If Mungkorn were to cook for me,
I'd rush home to eat every single day.
Mom, don't listen to him too much.
At his place, he has people cook for him every day.
No, no.
Regardless, you still have to cook for your husband once in a while.
I couldn't agree more.
You can't skip out on that.
You have to cook for your husband every now and then.
Here, have some nam prik ong.
Here.
- Thank you. - Eat it with some pork cracklings.
Here, eat some pork cracklings, too.
Can you feed me the pork cracklings?
Your hands work just fine, don't they?
Come on, you've got to take care of me.
Look at him, Mom.
It's so good, Mom.
Seriously delicious. So yummy!
I fried it myself.
Are you sure this thing still runs?
It does.
It just takes a bit of work to start the engine
since I haven't ridden it in ages.
I think
you should get a new one. This is too old. It's not gonna make it.
No, it's a waste of money.
Plus, I really love this bike.
It means a lot to me.
Why's that?
I saved up my own money to buy this.
I'm planning to take it to Chiang Mai with me, too.
- Whoa, alright. - Good job, Hunglay.
See? Ready to hit the road.
I hope it doesn't break down halfway.
No way.
This old guy can handle anything.
Trust me, Inspector.
Come on.
Okay.
If Hunglay is ready, then let's go.
Are you ready, though?
Alright, let's go, Hunglay!
Is it actually working?
Yeah, it just hasn't been started in a while.
I haven't started it in a while.
Alright, let's go!
Move it.
Wow, perfect timing.
They're performing the Sabat Chai drums right now.
Let's go check it out.
Let's go.
My bad.
I got a bit overexcited. I haven't seen this in a while.
You can keep holding my hand if you want. I don't mind.
Let's just watch the drum performance.
Is there anyone interested in trying the Sabat Chai drums?
Why don't you give it a shot?
Me? I don't even know how to play.
Just give it a try.
You're standing here with your eyes sparkling like that.
I'm sure you can do it.
I'll be right here cheering you on.
I'd rather not, Inspector.
Is there anyone interested in trying the Sabat Chai drums?
This guy right here!
- Hey, Inspector! - Please, come on up.
This guy wants to try it!
No!
Let's go.
How do I do it?
Just like this.
Well done!
What's up with you?
You've been smiling the whole time.
I didn't know you could play the drums that well.
I was just winging it.
Right now, let's forget about the drum beats.
I'd rather beat someone.
I just wanted you to be a bit more confident.
Anyway,
I'm so proud of my husband.
What are you looking at? The teddy bear?
Yeah, it's so cute.
A teddy bear in a police uniform.
That looks just like you.
Want it? I'll win it for you.
It's not as easy as firing a real gun.
They won't give these away easily,
or they'd go out of business.
But if there's anything you want,
I'll get it for you.
- Excuse me, beautiful. - Yes?
What do I do to get that teddy bear?
Oh, it's just a hundred baht.
You get five bullets,
and every single shot has to hit the target.
I told you.
This is not as easy as shooting a real gun.
Then we'll just keep playing until we win.
Here's a hundred, beautiful.
Thank you.
Since you're talking such a big game,
I challenge you...
to win it in just one try.
Challenge accepted.
We're only getting started.
Was that just pure luck?
Perfect aim.
It's pure luck.
Even John Wick would praise me.
More like John Wack.
I told you.
If there's anything you want,
I'll find a way to get it for you.
Don't get too cocky just yet.
You're definitely going to miss this one.
See?
I don't back down from a challenge, you know.
Once I'm challenged, I can do anything.
Yeah, yeah, whatever.
Thank you.
Do you want any more stuffed animals?
Should I win some more for you?
I could do this all night.
No.
Just this police teddy bear is enough.
Now that you've got the bear, I guess you don't care about me anymore.
Well, it is just too cute.
It looks so cuddly, too.
You think that bear is cuddly?
I'm much more cuddly, though.
Let's go cuddle on the Ferris wheel.
Two people, please.
- Go on, get in. - Does this go up high?
You can head to bed first.
I think I'll go sit in the gazebo by the pond for a bit.
It's been a while since I got to experience this.
I'm not sleepy yet.
Can I come with you?
There are a lot of mosquitoes, though.
I can't go to sleep, then.
I have to stay and make sure the mosquitoes don't get you.
It's fine. I can apply it myself.
Just keep playing your guitar. I'll do it for you.
That arm, too.
Okay.
I haven't played this in a while,
so I need to brush up on it a bit.
Try flirting with me using your guitar.
Do I still need to do that?
I'm already married and living in your house.
Of course you do.
I don't fall for people that easily, you know.
You've got to show me some moves before you can win my heart.
I'm not exactly the smooth type.
I'm pretty straightforward and easy to read.
I'm not very good at hiding my feelings.
Trust me, I know.
♪I have a heart to give, When will you receive it?♪
♪Can you hear it? My love, can you hear my wishes?♪
♪All of my heart, I've kept it all for you,♪
♪And all I want is for it to belong to you♪
♪If you ask how much I love you, I'll let you know♪
♪If you ask how much I care, I'll tell you so♪
♪I love you to the moon and back♪
♪That's how much love I have packed♪
♪About four hundred thousand miles, or even more than that♪
You're really good.
Does this count as you flirting with me?
That song was so romantic.
Think whatever you want.
It's just one of my favorite songs.
It doesn't mean anything about how I feel.
I wonder if there really is...
someone who could love you as much as the person in that song does.
I'd really like to know.
I honestly don't know.
I've never loved anyone that much, either.
Alright, whatever.
I'm going to take that song you just played
as our love confession.
Ouch!
Whoa, Inspector.
That's a huge mosquito.
It's feasting on your blood.
Seriously?
I thought you were going to kiss me.
You had me going there for a second.
You're pretty easy to read, too.
Come on, let's get some sleep
before the mosquitoes suck you dry.
Hey.
Can I sleep shirtless? I'm basically a human furnace.
No, you can't.
What if my mom saw you like that in the morning?
Come on.
Mungkorn...
There's something I really like about you.
What is it?
Honestly, it's quite a few things,
but there's one thing in particular that I really like.
It's that you're never ashamed to be yourself.
You like teddy bears.
You like bear-print pajamas.
You love all things cute.
To others, it might clash with being a cop,
but you don't care.
I find it quite charming, actually.
There's nothing to be ashamed of.
Cuteness and strength can definitely coexist.
Just like with you.
Right, Mungkorn.
Can I ask one thing of you?
If you're asking to cuddle my bear, the answer is no.
That's not it.
Can you please call me...
Thear the way your mom calls me?
I really like it.
Is that really a good idea?
Of course it is.
I think it sounds quite sweet.
Goodnight,
Thear.
Mungkorn.
♪I have a heart to give, when will it be received?♪
♪Can you hear it? My love, can you hear my wishes?♪
♪All of my heart, I've kept it all for you,♪
♪And all I want is for it to belong to you♪
♪If you ask how much I love you, I'll let you know♪
♪If you ask how much I care, I'll tell you so♪
♪I love you to the moon and back♪
♪That's how much love I have packed♪
♪About four hundred thousand miles, or even more than that♪
Do you have a ring on your ring finger?
Are you married, or did you just put it there?
Do you want to play a match with me?
If you can't play well, I can teach you.
I can tell at a glance
he's got his sights set on you.
What kind of sights?
Don't you like it?
We were only faking it last time.
Let's make it real this time.
Hey.
Seductive like this... Don't you like it?
But...
I'm here to serve you.
♪Trying so hard not to cross the line,♪
♪But the more I run, the more you're on my mind♪
♪If you're gonna love me, don't break the deal we made♪
♪Don't break my heart, remember what you said?♪
♪Let's call off the deal and let our hearts decide♪
♪From contracting parties to lovers, does that sound alright?♪
♪It's time you became mine♪